hey guys let's solve for x first we have
this equilateral triangle right here all
triangles have 180 degrees so if all
three angles are the same each angle is
going to be 60 degrees next let's look
at this regular pentagon the formula for
the sum of the interior angles of a
polygon is n minus 2 times 180 where n
is the number of sides of the polygon
for a pentagon it has five sides and
this will give us the sum of all the
interior angles if we want to know how
big each angle is we're going to divide
by 5 and this will give us 108 degrees
so this one's 108 this one's 108 this
one's 108. this one down here we already
have the 60s so we're going to need
additional 48 and same thing for this
one an additional 48. but next let's
look at this right triangle right here
if we added these three angles they're
all going to add up to 180 degrees the
48 Plus 90 is 138 and if we subtract 138
from both sides we get x equals 42 and
that is our answer for X how exciting